Now, there’s a huge sale
on some fish in season.
Fresh, plump mackerels!
Get two for $5!
Flounders in the winter
and mackerels in the fall.
It’s mackerel season!
The sale is on right now
at the first floor seafood corner.
CANNED HAM
20XX
EARTHQUAKE
CIVILIZATION
DESTROYED
ECONOMY
COLLAPSED
NEW ERA OF
BARBARISM
I thought the world would end.
I thought I’d just die there alone.
But...
I guess it wasn’t my time yet.
It’s like I was born again that day.
Hwang Gung Apartment
was a new world.
The survivors made a market there.
8th FLOOR
HUMAN MARKET
NO EXTERNAL CONDOMS ALLOWED
Get ready to sell.
Sir! Please! Just this once?
No! Please!
They weren’t only selling goods.
It has nothing to do with me.
Anyway, the only way
we could live like this
was all thanks to Chairman PARK.
9th FLOOR
TYRANT
MARKET ECONOMY
HWANG GUNG APARTMENTS
I thought that’s the way
life had to be.
Until the girl came, that is.
She changed everything.
CONCRETE MARKET
Hello, visitors to
our Hwang Gung Market.
If you bring goods, you found
in the ruined world to our market,
you can buy anything.
Enjoy shopping with us!
The parking lot market
has oil and electronics for sale.
The 1st floor has water and necessities.
The 2nd floor has clothes
and a barbershop.
From the 3rd floor and up,
we have nice residential units.
Nothing but your body to sell?
Then you can come to
the 8th floor to sell.
The 8th floor is to comfort you...
I heard you can get everything here.
Got canned food?
Remember to leave
when the siren rings.
If you don’t,
you’ll be deemed as a thief.
Don’t do anything stupid.
You’re not fit for the 8th floor.
Go on.
The 8th floor?
Only losers with nothing to sell
go there.
Go on.
Open your ears and hearts!
Listen to the world!
It’s all written in the Bible!
Read the Bible!
It’s already written in there!
In wind, rain or shine,
thank you for coming
to our market today!
We, the merchants’ association,
have an announcement.
As always,
any deals made outside
our association will be punished.
We hope you enjoy shopping with us!
Here. Take the money, please.
Damn.
Cash is useless.
Bring stuff we can use.
Just take it and go.
PHYSICS
Verse 18!
“The woman you saw is...”
You must believe what I say!
Open your ears and hearts!
You must listen to heaven!
You bastard!
How dare you!
You can’t do this to me!
Even if the world ended...
So what?
Jesus sacrificed himself
on the hill of Golgotha.
Damn.
He told everyone to share
and live together!
What?
You know that thieves were nailed
next to him, right?
Grab him.
What are you doing?
Wait! Hold on!
Not again.
Who are they?
They’re PARK Sang-yong’s bagmen.
Are there only boys?
PARK takes collections
like a gangster.
He took in some bastards
and set ’em up to collect.
Hello!
Here.
Min-chul pays 3 cans!
So the young jerks think
they’re big and act tough.
What’s left?
The liquor shop.
How cute.
What the hell?
It’s closed?
Why are the bastards not working?
- What reeks?
- Open the door.
Okay
What’s wrong?
- Open it.
- Okay!
Hurry up, man!
Shit!
Bro! I think they’re all dead.
Move!
What the fuck did they drink?
It was obviously an accident.
Stupid!
- Stupid retards.
- Take ’em
Fuck. We’re screwed.
Where’s our canned food?
What the hell?
Stupid bastard!
Go find it now!
Shit!
Roll up your sleeves.
Let me see your bag.
Fuck! What if they left with it?
Damn it! Follow me!
Where?
To close off the gates!
But there’s time left till closing!
Wait!
Hold on!
What are you doing?
It’s no big deal.
A thief is on the loose.
Don’t open it till the market ends.
Did you find the bag?
Fuck!
We’re always behind PARK Chul-min
in collecting payment.
Can’t you do your damn job?
How could you lose the bag?
- I didn’t do it on purpose!
- Stop making excuses!
- Stop.
Cut it out! Damn it!
Tae-jin!
I found this on the 2nd floor.
Look.
If we don’t give him the collection,
we’re fucked.
The duffle bag...
The girl with the duffle bag!
She’s still in here!
Find her!
No luck?
Look for her properly!
Did you look down every corner?
Yes!
Look again!
Hey!
- Duffle bag?
- No sign of her.
- Damn it!
- Fuck.
Let’s go this way.
I’ll take these, please.
HAN Se-jung?
Good thing I stayed alive.
How’d you come here?
It’s far from your town.
What’s this?
It’s nothing.
No! They’re needle marks.
I have no other choice here
to survive from PARK Sang-yong
on the 9th floor.
What about your little sister?
You’d do anything to live?
You give me pleasure,
then I give you what you need.
That’s our deal.
Only I need to make deals.
I’ll tell you about Se-hee
at home later.
Let’s get out of here.
- Let’s go and...
- I want to leave with you too.
To a place where we can be happy.
But...
There’s no such place anymore.
The market will close
in 10 minutes.
Anyone who enters or leaves
after closing will be executed.
It’s not so bad here and it’s safe.
Just stay here and live with me.
The market will close
in 10 minutes.
- Anyone who...
- Let’s go to my place.
Stay there for now.
I’ll explain everything later.
It’s dangerous now.
Wait at my place.
He-ro.
I have to go early today.
I have no choice but to stay here.
What are you going to do
after you graduate?
When we graduate,
let’s move to a place
where we can live together.
How about it?
Great. Let’s go together.
Welcome.
Have a seat.
You like pasta, right?
Let’s have some beef too
for a treat.
Wait.
Parsley!
I’m out of parsley.
Se-jung, go to my storage?
The parsley should be there.
Bring me some?
What was that?
The garden! Look!
Over there!
What the hell is it?
Fuck. What the hell?
What happened?
How did this happen?
It’s the chairman’s girl.
One, two, three!
Grab her arm, stupid!
Hold her properly!
Never held a girl before?
Come on! Hurry up!
Move.
Damn.
It’s so cold.
No...
You bitch!
Sneaky rat!
Where’d you hide the cans?
Tell me where they are, bitch!
We gotta find the bag.
Take her.
EARTHQUAKE
CONFLICTS
RAINY SEASON
SLEEPING WITH THE ENEMY
I wonder what Se-jung did wrong.
He favored her so much.
Yeah, why’d he kill her?
She must’ve rubbed him
the wrong way.
Once, I saw her grimace
when he touched her.
Then why did she go
whenever he called her?
She has diabetes.
She’ll die without insulin shots.
But who controls all the medicine
that comes in here?
Here.
Chairman PARK.
Once you live here,
you can’t live without PARK’s meds.
You can hate PARK,
but you can’t leave here.
Watch it!
Call him Chairman PARK.
Show some respect, jerk.
Shit. I’m gonna puke.
You’re too loyal.
Can I have unit 109
where HAN Se-jung used to live?
- Why you little...
- Shut up.
Quiet!
Hey.
Where’d you hide your bag?
Tell me where it is!
Why are you looking for my bag?
Our food cans are in there!
Got proof that I stole them?
Wait outside.
Look.
Tell me where the goods are
and I’ll let you walk free.
It’s never been imagined
or done here,
but I’ll do it for you.
Right...
I just want to go back too.
You’re asking for it.
Se-jung?
No!
It’s dangerous now.
Wait at my place.
She has diabetes.
I’ll tell you everything.
I can explain.
Se-jung...
She didn’t have diabetes.
What did you say?
What?
What about your little sister?
You’d do anything to live here?
You look alike!
Of course! We’re sisters.
- Cool.
- Of course we look alike.
Se-hee...
Snap to it!
Where’s your damn bag!
Did she fess up?
We looked everywhere,
but couldn’t find it.
No idea.
I don’t have them, assholes.
I’ll rip your mouth!
Damn it.
We’ll rip up your mouth, bitch!
Bros! Tae-jin!
Hey!
I warned you not to bang
on the door!
We got a problem!
Chul-min and his boys
are coming with weapons!
Fuck!
Where?
Hi, retards!
What the fuck are you doing
in my turf?
Hi!
I heard all the liquor dealers died.
I came to set my boys up here.
Are you nuts?
I heard you’re hiding something.
Lost your collection yesterday?
Screw you, bastard!
Fight me.
Can’t, huh? You loser!
Before the world came to this,
I never heard of you.
Be honest.
You heard of me, right?
Ever got bullied and
mugged by me?
What the hell?
You’re really asking for it.
So what if I am?
You son of a bitch!
Why?
Scared?
Like hell I am!
I’m hyped up to kill you.
Attention all merchants!
The aftershock is over.
Don’t mind it and
get ready to open shops.
Are you okay, bro?
Chairman PARK is coming!
I’ll let you off for today.
Listen, boys.
How about coming under me?
I’ll pay you guys well.
Too bad.
I’m not letting you off today!
Bastard!
Son of a bitch.
I didn’t come here for this.
But you got on my nerves!
Go on! Fight me, bastard!
Try it, asshole!
Bastard!
Son of a bitch!
You asked for it!
Hey!
What’s going on?
Answer me!
Chul-min said he’d open up
a shop on my turf, sir.
And he called you a...
Tae-jin lost his collection, sir.
It was stolen, sir.
I said I’d help,
then the bastard blew up on me.
Is that true?
No, sir.
I never asked for help.
I mean...
Was your collection really stolen?
Can I have unit 109
where HAN Se-jung used to live?
We have the thief in unit 209, sir.
Fuck.
Let Chul-min’s boys
open shop here.
You!
You’re lucky that I’m not
throwing you out right now.
She has diabetes.
Se-hee!
Sis?
Why’d you come so late?
I...
Se-hee?
Se-hee!
Sis...
Se-jung said...
If he knows I’m sick,
PARK Sang-yong will come after me.
So instead of me,
she made needle marks
on her arms.
You’d do anything to live here?
Se-jung died because of me.
HAN Se-hee!
No!
She didn’t die because of you.
He-ro.
You could die if you get caught.
Don’t worry about me
and run away from here.
HAN Se-hee!
Don’t get any ideas.
Just think about living.
I’ll live here with you
till you’re safe.
You can’t just live here
because you want to.
Se-jung could only live here
because of her deals with PARK.
Don’t worry.
I have stuff to make deals too.
What are you doing here?
I took your things in the trunk too.
I admit I stole from you.
What do you want?
If you think I’ll let you off,
forget it.
This place is a market.
Let’s run a business with this.
Everyone thinks
this is stolen and gone anyway.
What the hell?
I’ll turn this into 10 times more
within 2 months.
Why would I trust you?
This is all we need.
I’ll make 10 times more
with this within 2 months.
Soon, it’ll be the rainy season.
It’s all about supply and demand
and the right timing.
My plan starts with this.
DEALS
MARKET ECONOMY
WATER &amp; FIRE
THE WAY TO THE TOP
We can’t last like this.
Shit!
Get him!
Stop!
Get them!
Son of a bitch!
Hey.
Why’d you make him faint?
Wanna carry him?
LEE Mi-sun...
Hold on a bit longer.
I’ll get you out.
Hey! KIM Tae-jin is coming.
Tae-jin! Went to unit 802 again?
LEE Mi-sun never has a day off
thanks to you.
Is it love or...
Going through puberty?
Back off, jerk.
What’s it to you?
It’s good for me, retard.
You’re paying in my turf.
We’re running real low
on cigarettes here.
But someone said the 1st floor
is full of ’em.
So I went down myself to buy ’em.
But a pack of cigarettes
were selling for one canned food.
One can for one pack.
A can for a pack.
So I asked how many cans
I could get for selling a pack.
You get 3 cans.
3 cans for a pack.
They said 3 cans.
What kind of deal is that?
What’s it to you
how much I buy or sell for?
Then I saw something interesting.
Curious?
See these?
I marked our cigarette packs
like this.
I sold one for two cans,
but you’re selling them back.
What are you up to?
I guess
folks know they can buy from you
then sell to me to make money.
Fuck! How dare you mess around
with the price!
We’ll both go under.
Stupid asshole.
I only need to beat you.
If you’re scared,
sell for cheaper.
I know you can’t, loser!
He found out later than I thought.
Look.
Trust is everything with deals.
It’s building relationships in a world
with no family or anything!
If we’re in this together,
give me something to trust you.
I explained it to you.
Explained what?
You said to buy up
Chul-min’s cigarettes with the cans,
then buy oil and solid fuels
with the rest.
You call that an explanation?
Stupid morons.
Fuck.
Who knows what today’s date is?
At a time like this,
who cares about the date?
Only the weather matters.
Today is September 23rd.
You were counting?
You weren’t?
The rainy season will start soon.
What would be needed
the most then?
Raise and sell the solid fuels
for 3 times more then.
Son of a gun!
If you quit smoking,
when is it the hardest?
The third day.
Then for 3 days,
say we’re out and don’t sell.
From the 4th day,
sell a pack for 5 cans.
Pour it properly.
Five cans, please.
Here.
Solid fuels.
Two cigarette packs.
Line up straight! Hey!
6 cans of oil.
Give me the canned goods first.
Hurry up!
Solid fuels! Oil! Cigarettes!
We got lots here!
Bring your canned goods!
Five cans!
Didn’t you collect?
Business was bad
because of the rain, sir.
Goods aren’t coming in, either.
Is it raining only in your area?
It’s because Tae-jin hoarded...
Hoarded?
Why do you always blame me?
I just prepared for
the rainy season, sir.
Good at risk management, huh?
Hidden skills come out
during a crisis, right?
Right.
If you leave it to me,
I won’t let it rain to the 8th floor.
Wouldn’t that be more effective
for the market?
Chul-min’s gang
needs to make a living too.
Don’t get greedy.
Well, then...
Tae-jin can run the parking lot
to the 2nd floor again.
How are we supposed
to make a living, sir?
You have the 8th floor.
Here.
We checked 2 days ago.
Checking your blood sugar level
after meals is important.
Watch.
Look.
You gotta do this on your own
when I’m gone.
What if you get sick again
and I’m not here?
Can’t you brush your hair?
Well...
I don’t really have to.
CHOI He-ro! It’s me.
What is it?
Hyun-min is sick.
Let’s go on watch together.
Okay.
This is awesome!
It’s been years since I had
a cold drink.
Thanks, He-ro.
Don’t drink it all.
Save some for Hyun-min.
He’s sick.
He shouldn’t drink this.
What?
Got something to say?
From tomorrow,
we’re running the parking lot
till the 4th floor.
Great.
Anyway...
That’s that.
- I admit...
- It’s all thanks to me?
I know. Stop mumbling.
I know we got off
on the wrong foot,
but we’re a team now.
Anyway,
if we keep working together,
maybe we can even
take over more higher floors.
Then maybe I’ll get closer
with the Chairman too.
- Because of me...
- No, it’s not!
Se-jung!
I just do what he wants,
then I get what I want.
It’s someone else’s fault.
Really?
Just think about staying alive
and nothing else.
I’ll get revenge.
Then why don’t you take over
the 9th floor instead of PARK?
Never thought you could live
in unit 902?
You never dreamed about becoming
the king of this market?
And stab Chairman PARK
in the back?
Why not?
It’s not like he’s your dad.
How was your life before?
Why do you ask?
Tell me.
How did you survive
and come here?
- It’s nothing.
- Then, tell me.
I...
I was born dirt poor
and struggled through life.
Then the world got destroyed.
Maybe that’s how
I was able to survive.
What about you?
I was at a convenience store
in the east end.
While fighting for the food there,
I got stabbed in the leg.
It got infected and I had a fever.
When the food ran out,
the gang said they’d move out.
The bastards voted in front of me.
Then the leader of the gang
came to me
and said sorry,
but they’re leaving me behind.
In that basement,
I was left to die alone.
But then someone came.
It was Chairman PARK.
If it wasn’t for him then,
I would just died
down there.
Even after I came here,
I almost died a few times.
But LEE Mi-sun saved me.
I owe Chairman PARK
and LEE Mi-sun a lot.
Aren’t you sleeping?
I will.
It’s gotta start from
PARK Sang-yong’s end,
but I have no way to meet him.
KIM Tae-jin
owes PARK his life,
so he won’t budge.
He totally loves
and worships the bastard.
With a sick heart,
how would you know?
Se-hee.
I gotta deal directly
with the medicine sellers.
You’ll try to get meds
without PARK knowing?
What if you get caught?
I need to get caught by PARK.
Line up. We got lots of water.
Pay the cans first.
One by one.
What the hell?
Why is it trickling?
What’s the matter?
The water...
- Sir!
- What is it?
Sir!
What’s that stench?
The sewer path over there
is filled with water!
I found some beast masks.
No one can come here
through the sewers!
Damn beasts.
The beasts think they can
take over our market?
It’s a curse.
Because we’re living well here.
If the water stops running,
we’ll all die this winter!
Watch your damn mouth!
Come here.
I think it’s from the sewers
getting blocked.
Who can fix this?
Anyone?
Damn.
It’s because the Han River overflowed
to the sewers after the rainy season.
What?
The well water comes from
the mountain back there, right?
If the pipe burst there,
we can reroute the water supply
with another pipe in a few days.
Got a map of the area, sir?
Is this a girl’s intuition?
It’s hydrodynamics.
What?
Like unclogging a toilet.
Hey!
Shut up.
Give me some helpers
and I’ll fix it in 3 days.
Did you have lunch?
Wanna have lunch with me?
Why’d you step up?
Don’t you know
when to stay put?
You saw the beast masks!
The beasts did this!
Wanna become their bait?
How dare you speak up to the Chairman
like HAN Se-jung.
Remember what happened?
Come on. That’s different.
People are talking.
Se-jung had red spots all over.
She could’ve been poisoned.
Mister.
What’s this?
It’s for listening to music.
It’s like a computer, right?
After investing the area,
you’re saying we can have water
back in a few days?
Yes.
Give me a few men
and I’ll get it done.
Okay, sure.
Why? Don’t like steak?
Se-jung loved it.
You don’t know her, huh?
She’s a friend.
How old are you?
I’m eighteen.
You’re the same age.
I haven’t seen a girl here my age.
Right.
She died.
How’d you know the problem
right away like that?
It’s a waste for you to be
with KIM Tae-jin.
Did well in school, huh?
What did you want to become?
A prosecutor.
Prosecutor?
Then I’ll be worth more
at law firms.
Law firm?
When the world collapsed like this,
those in power couldn’t adjust
and died off first.
But me?
My life was a jungle
in the first place.
Who needs the law?
I rule this world now.
What do you think I used to do?
A pharmaceutical company salesman.
A salaryman.
I served in the union
and worked my butt off.
I learned one thing
from all that.
Neither the company nor the union
get what they want.
But the moles who kiss up
to the company,
they get major pay hikes
and get everything they want.
I realized companies or unions
can’t come out on top.
Only moles win.
The way I see it,
you’re fit to be a winner.
Are you telling me to be a mole?
It’s just...
I don’t trust people much.
Not unless I know their weak spots.
Then why do you trust me?
You tried to buy meds.
Heart medication.
I gotta deal directly
with the medicine sellers.
You give me information
and I give you
heart medication.
Pretty simple, huh?
Your life is in my hands.
See you from time to time.
What will He-ro do?
No idea.
Did you see that pretty girl earlier?
Yeah! She was pretty like Se-jung.
Right.
Want me to keep you locked in?
How many cans
did you pay for this?
Se-jung wanted to have that.
I’m sorry about earlier.
I know it’s because
you’re worried about me.
Se-jung asked me
to take care of you.
I know she would’ve...
No one saw you, right?
I know you’re in there.
Hi.
Why are you here at this hour?
We’re looking for a thief
who snuck in today.
He’s not on our floor
that’s for sure.
Where did he go?
Excuse me.
I never heard about a thief.
Nice place you’ve got.
Know HAN Se-jung?
Who’s that?
A pretty girl.
But she fell to her death
on the day you came here.
What a coincidence!
HAN Se-jung used to live here.
So?
Well,
I saw someone who looked
eerily like HAN Se-jung today.
My boys said they saw her
go inside here.
Then it hit me.
Maybe before CHOI He-ro,
that mystery girl lived here first.
Se-jung’s sister is here, isn’t she?
She could be older,
but my guess is she’s younger
’cuz Se-jung protected her
by going to PARK.
You’re out of your mind,
but go ahead and search all you want.
I can look for her later.
What are you trying to pull?
That’s what I want to ask you.
Trying to get revenge for Se-jung?
Then you chose the wrong cards.
Tae-jin, the loser,
doesn’t have what it takes.
He thinks of PARK as his dad.
What makes you any different?
I’m totally different.
I want to rip up PARK,
that bastard, to pieces.
What did Dong Zhuo’s underling
Lü Bu do?
Don’t know, huh?
The Records of
the Three Kingdoms.
If I were you,
I’d side with Lü Bu.
What if I don’t?
Then I’ll tell PARK about you
and make sure Se-jung’s sister
works like hell on the 8th floor.
You asshole!
I’ll give you a week.
If you don’t give me an answer,
no deal.
Sleep well, pretty face.
He-ro.
What are you gonna do?
I don’t like Chul-min.
He seems dangerous.
At least we have the same goal.
I don’t think Tae-jin does.
I’m sorry.
It’s my fault.
I got caught ’cuz of this.
I’ll throw it out.
Let me borrow it.
WIRETAPPING
ENSUING SIN
CHAIRMAN’S INTENT
You want to get LEE Mi-sun
out of room 802, right?
I found a way.
Really?
Chul-min and his gang want to start
the liquor shop well,
but they’re low on water.
The deal is we get them
lots of water for Mi-sun.
One bottle per person!
Drink sparingly!
Okay.
There’s a limit to how much water
each person can buy now.
Just like with the cigarettes,
say if they sell water to us,
they’ll make double.
I know.
I’ll tell the boys.
Sorry...
It’s a deal.
What? Really?
I’ll start by taking KIM Tae-jin out.
But I have three conditions.
If you takeover the 9th floor,
I manage the meds.
And
promise you’ll leave Se-hee alone.
Okay.
You’ll set up a drugstore?
But that’s the best deal.
Don’t change the subject
and promise me.
Promise.
So?
What’s your plan?
I don’t want your boys
to know my plan.
That’s my third condition.
Don’t worry about him.
I heard he can hear a bit.
Geun-seok!
Geun-seok, you retard!
See? He can’t hear.
Now.
What’s your plan?
What the fuck!
I’ll poison the water
that PARK has saved.
I want to take over things
in good shape.
It’s already tainted.
Shit!
What the fuck?
It’s just the beginning.
Sit back and watch.
Move!
Out of my way!
What the fuck!
Who the hell is behind this?
The guard said he saw someone
with a beast mask on.
He was on night watch here.
He said he saw a beast
lurking by the fence up there.
Why didn’t you report it, stupid!
You went to check,
but it was gone?
Are you sure the beasts did this?
It was their mask,
but not the clothes.
It wasn’t dressed like
the beasts.
There’s no water today.
What? You came to clean
or something?
Crazy!
Want us to drink bleach and die?
Crazy! You stupid bitch!
The main ingredient is
sodium hypochlorite.
With water it dissolves and sterilizes
bacteria and microorganisms.
I gotta calculate
and add the exact amount.
So move out of my way.
Calculate and try it.
325 litres...
From tomorrow,
it’ll be drinkable.
Good. I’ll call you.
Let’s have dinner later.
Damn.
Who the hell is it this time?
Damn it!
Who is it?
Shit.
What is it?
About the water...
I know who did it.
You’re gonna squeal?
Yup.
Just order your boys to say
that they saw a beast do it.
I found this in unit 209.
Okay.
But the mask alone is too weak.
Are you sure KIM Tae-jin did this?
How do you know for sure?
Tae-jin and his boys
bought water yesterday
with all the cans they had.
Tell your men to go and check.
I’m going.
People will get suspicious.
Wait.
Hold still.
You should take this.
Good job.
Close the door behind you.
Hi.
Why are you here?
Don’t worry.
I didn’t come for her job.
We can’t touch her now anyway.
What do you mean?
That woman...
No one can have her.
She’s done selling.
What the fuck do you mean?
She’s the new HAN Se-jung.
The chairman, you respect so much,
claimed her as his.
What about the water?
What about it?
If I give you water,
you let her go.
Didn’t you make a deal
with He-ro?
Oh, that?
Sorry, man. Too bad.
The deal is off.
Son of a bitch!
Drink lots of water.
It’s good for your health.
What happened?
Explain it to me.
I said I’d get you out.
Tell me what the hell happened!
I’m not going by myself.
I want to get revenge on PARK, too.
He’s more of a devil
than you know.
You called?
Yes.
KIM Tae-jin...
Get rid of him.
What do you mean, sir?
Kill him.
He was a goner
since he touched my water.
Managing the boys will be a problem,
if you kill him, huh?
Then get Chul-min to do it.
That way the boys
won’t band together.
Right.
Hey!
Tell Chul-min to come here.
Yes, sir!
It’s about killing someone
you used to eat with.
You don’t even flinch?
Listen.
I set the table.
Just say yes to him.
Don’t worry.
Adults love a good kid like me.
Just hold up your end.
What is it?
PARK says to come to
his place at 9 p.m.
Why did he tell you that?
I bumped into him. Why?
You can count on me, right?
Of course.
When should I do the job, sir?
I told you.
I’ll get us to rule here.
What are you doing here?
Came alone?
You said to come alone.
You’re too trusting.
What are you gonna do?
From now on...
Where’s the chairman?
Here.
What’s this?
This is the chairman?
Close the door behind you.
Thank you.
Want a drink?
Yes, sir!
You can count on me, right?
The chairman’s intent.
Of course.
When should I do the job, sir?
I told him to come
around 9 p.m.
Kill him on his way here.
You brought him, gave him meds,
and saved his life.
I thought
he was special to you.
That’s what Tae-jin thinks.
Well,
I brought him thinking
he’d be useful,
but he just got weaker,
so I just left him to die.
Then LEE Mi-sun saved his life.
The meds that I gave him
were just cheap vitamins.
It’s not worth using antibiotics
on a mama’s boy like him, you know?
I told him to come alone.
He does whatever I say,
so he’ll come.
When he comes out, just kill him.
Yes, sir.
How the fuck can he do this to us?
What now?
We’ll do whatever you want.
PARK Sang-yong
always said this to me.
Stop acting like a kid
and become an adult.
But for us,
the world ended
before we could grow up.
No one spoon-feeds us.
We gotta survive by ourselves
and become adults on our own!
After tonight,
there won’t be anyone older here
than us.
What about PARK Chul-min?
It won’t be easy with just us.
Did the bastard run away?
It’s been over an hour...
It’s already done.
I made a deal.
I KNOW YOU’RE PARK SANG-YONG’S MOLE
You said you’re going to the 8th floor,
but you met PARK instead in secret.
Do your boys know that?
Hey, Geun-seok.
Geun-seok, you retard.
You must get migraines
from your hearing loss,
so he must’ve offered you
the meds like me.
KNOW HOW LU BU DIED?
If you help me,
all the migraine meds
that come in will be yours.
And PARK Chul-min’s spot too.
Now, you’re the same as us.
Bye, man. See you in hell.
Lü Bu died from
an underling’s betrayal.
Men aren’t the only ones
who read that book.
She said to tell you.
It’ll get noisy outside,
but don’t come out.
Did PARK catch on?
He’s making dinner now.
He has no clue.
He invited someone.
It was the same with Se-jung.
She was invited for dinner.
Look at this.
Maybe someone else killed her.
RED SPOTS WILL FORM
ON THE SKIN
CAN PURIFY WASTEWATER AND MAKE
POISON WITH BLEACH
Why advertise that
you can make poison?
Se-jung had red spots too.
Did she take your concoction?
I think she was poisoned.
You said she had red spots.
It’s a side effect of that poison.
LEE Mi-sun, the woman you
and Tae-jin are trying to rescue,
used to work at a lab.
She must want to get on
PARK’s good side.
To do that,
Se-jung has to be taken out.
There’s no proof.
I’ll check it out.
If Tae-jin takes over tonight,
wouldn’t everything be hers?
I’ll go and check tonight.
You stay put right here.
Wait.
Hold still.
You should take this.
Wait.
She should’ve asked for it first.
CHOI He-ro lives in unit 109, right?
Yes, she does.
Dinner is ready.
Should I call LEE Mi-sun, sir?
I’ll eat with her tomorrow.
I’ll go and meet
someone else tonight.
MOMMY WILL COME TO YOU SOON.
IT’S ALMOST OVER.
How dare you!
You think Mi-sun wanted to go
to the 9th floor to rule like you?
She’s nothing like you.
I’m sorry.
I read everything.
PARK Sang-yong...
Right.
To live here,
he said everyone had to work.
Then he sent our kids
through the rundown buildings.
It’s okay.
I’ll wait for you right here.
That’s good!
From then on,
PARK kept his distance from us.
Se-jung tried to help us.
She wanted to kill him
more than anyone.
That night...
You’re the only one
who can get close to him.
Thanks, Se-jung.
She just had to put it
in PARK’s food.
But something went wrong.
Mi-sun! LEE Mi-sun!
Are you okay?
CHOI He-ro.
Why are you here?
What is it?
I heard PARK took a girl
from the first floor.
Se-hee...
BETRAYAL UPON
BETRAYAL
What are you saying?
You mean,
because of HAN Se-jung
and her sister,
you used us all this time
to get revenge?
Huh?
That’s enough.
We gotta save Se-jung’s sister first.
PARK rounded up all his men
on the 9th floor.
We can’t attack as planned.
They have Se-jung’s sister, too.
Think she’s okay?
You said the water
will come out today.
When it does,
PARK’s gang will come down to drink.
Let’s attack then.
It’s not coming.
What?
There’s no water.
I made it all up.
Shit...
What?
Why the hell did you do that?
Because then PARK
will give orders to kill you.
How can we control
the water coming or not?
The pipes are just frozen.
What did you just say?
Did you tell PARK
that I dirtied the well?
What the fuck!
Think you’re any different
from PARK?
Who wouldn’t do anything
to protect someone?
We’re all the same.
If Mi-sun put that in PARK’s food,
it would’ve been over.
We need a new plan.
Water...
We have nothing but water.
Thanks to you, we’re flat broke
and just have water on the 2nd floor.
We’ll help you.
You said trust is everything
with deals, right?
Trust me just this once.
Chairman!
Sir!
Water!
Water is coming out.
We’re saved, sir!
Let’s go!
Out of my way!
Drink up!
Damn!
She did it.
Go on! Drink!
How did He-ro...
Go now.
What about you?
I’ll pack some insulin.
Hurry! Go!
- Boys!
- Yes?
Wait!
Who’s watching the top floor?
What?
Stupid retards!
Damn!
Let’s go.
Hey!
What’s that?
You bastard!
Assholes! Stay back!
He-ro said to come here.
You must be Se-hee.
Come here.
Damn it.
Kid.
Think you could take me out?
A girl like you?
- After everything I did to get here?
- Damn.
You talk too much.
Jungle, my ass.
You little bitch!
If you were living in a jungle,
I was living in sheer hell.
I’m still alive to kill you.
You don’t deserve to live.
Kid.
Are you doing this
’cuz of Se-jung?
I know bastards like you well.
Thought Se-jung had no one?
That’s why you killed her.
But you’re wrong.
Se-jung had me and Se-hee, too.
You’re laughing?
I didn’t kill Se-jung.
Cut the bullshit.
You poisoned her
and killed her that night.
Poison?
What poison?
I see.
That’s why she ate so well
that night?
Parsley!
I’m out of parsley.
Se-jung, go to my storage?
The parsley should be there.
Bring me some?
Oh, cheese!
I forgot to sprinkle some cheese.
How could I forget the cheese?
Jeez...
There.
Hurry up, let’s eat.
Parsley.
Eat up.
Why are you staring?
- Are you okay?
- Hmm?
Why?
Nothing.
There was no cheese here before.
I forgot, so I sprinkled some on.
Really...
Why didn’t I notice that?
You know what?
No matter how much you drink wine
and act all big,
no one will ever truly love you.
Why ruin the mood,
you crazy bitch.
Come here!
Hey!
Wait!
Come back!
What are you doing there?
Come down.
No.
Hey!
So,
Se-jung died
because of her sister
and you’re acting up like this?
You’re so cute I could kill you.
Crazy bastard.
Fuck.
Why do you think
I only have him here?
All the other boys went downstairs.
That girl went down, didn’t she?
Back off!
Stop!
Wait!
Stop, you bitches!
If anyone moves,
I’ll slit her throat.
Don’t worry. Just run away!
I’m sick of living like this!
No!
I hope it doesn’t get too bloody.
My boys have been
pretty stressed lately.
They’re brutal.
Cut the fuckin’ bullshit.
It’s about time you died.
What the fuck are you saying?
Cut the bullshit!
I poisoned the water.
No poop and pee this time,
but real poison.
Drink it up!
The poison meant for you...
I put it all in the well water.
No!
What?
What the fuck did you do!
I never let poison in here.
Detergent and makeup
can be made with poison.
It’s a gift from the 8th floor.
Fuck.
Die.
CHOI He-ro!
He-ro!
Just die...
PARK Sang-yong! Open up!
CHOI He-ro!
He-ro!
He-ro! Wake up.
Are you okay?
He-ro...
Damn bitches.
How dare you!
I fed you and let you live here.
Fuck.
How dare...
Damn bitches...
Just shut up, you son of a bitch.
Hey, I’m...
What?
You mean, you’re sorry?
No one needs to rule here.
We can just live well together.
Can I ask a favor though?
What is it?
Make it like a school.
Teach how to survive.
Protect the people.
This world is new to everyone.
Right.
- Someone must rebuild civilization...
- No.
Nothing grand like that.
I just...
I just miss school.